awesemo.com 2019-04-08

# Privacy Policy - Awesemo.com

Awesemo.com LLC (“Awesemo.com”) understands your desire to have your personal information protected. We respect your concerns about privacy and describe below the types of information we collect, how we may use it, and with whom we may share it. Please contact us at support@awesemo.com with any questions you may have.

**Personal Information**

We may request that you provide personal information if you contact us, create a Awesemo.com user account, request technical support, provide feedback, participate in a promotion, or seek business-related opportunities.

In order to create an account on Awesemo.com, you will need to select a user name and password and provide a valid e-mail address. We may also collect your time zone preference and location, should you choose to supply the latter.

We have taken appropriate security measures to protect your personal information. These measures protect your data from misuse or unauthorized access.

**Aggregate Information**

We may collect aggregate and non-personal information when users visit our website. This includes, but is not limited to, how many users visit our site, pages accessed, and countries users came from. By collecting this information, we may learn how to best tailor our website to our visitors. We may track domain names, IP addresses, location, browser types, and other technical information from users who visit our site.

**Cookies**

At times, we may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Awesemo.com. These companies may use information about your visits to Awesemo.com and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Internet-Based Online Advertising and Google Analytics**

This section of our Privacy Policy provides details about interest-based online advertising (also called “targeted advertising”, “remarketing”, or “behavioural advertising”), Google Analytics, and your choices with respect to this type of advertising.

We use Google Analytics’ third-party audience data such as age, gender, and interests to better understand the behavior of our customers and work with companies that collect information about your online activities to provide advertising targeted to suit your interests and preferences.  For example, you may see certain ads on this website or other websites because we contract with Google and other similar companies to target our ads based on information we or they have collected, including information that was collected through automated means (such as cookies and web beacons).  These companies also use automated technologies to collect information when you click on our ads, which helps track and manage the effective of our marketing efforts.

You may opt out of the automated collection of information by third-party ad networks for the purpose of delivering advertisements tailored t your interests, by visiting the consumer opt-out page for the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising at http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ and edit or opt-out your Google Display Network ads’ preferences at http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/. Because those opt-oit and preference control pages are specific to the individual browser used to visit it, and because that page is not operated by Awesemo.com, we are unable to perform the opt-outs on your behalf.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

When we collect information from you, we may use it for a number of purposes, including to:

  * Provide you with the products and services you request
  * Communicate with you about your accounts or transactions with us and send you information about features on our sites and applications or changes to our policies
  * Consistent with local law and choices and controls that may be available to you we may use information collected from you or from devices associated with you, to: (1) send you offers and promotions for our products and services or third party products and services; (2) personalize content and experiences; (3) provide you with advertising based on your activity on our sites and applications and on third-party sites and applications.
  * Optimize or improve our products, services and operations
  * Detect investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal

**Opting Out of Emails**

If you do not wish to continue receiving our e-mails, you can opt out by clicking “Opt Out” in the footer of the e-mail or by contacting us at support@Awesemo.com.

**Third Party Privacy Policies**

Please consult the Privacy Policies of third parties we work with, such as ad networks, for their general practices.

**Legal Information**

Awesemo.com respects your privacy and, under ordinary circumstances, will not disclose the personal or personally identifiable information you provide to us to third parties. There may be circumstances, however, when such disclosure is necessary and therefore will occur. For instance, Awesemo.com may be required by law to disclose this information to government officials and judicial/law enforcement officers, such as in response to a subpoena, warrant, court demand, or other properly issued legal process.  Additionally, such disclosure may be necessary for us to protect and enforce our legal rights. Consistent with this, we reserve the right to disclose personal or personally identifiable information to third parties where necessary – in our sole discretion – to protect the integrity of the site or where other pressing business need presents itself.

**Links to External Websites**

On Awesemo.com, there may be links to companies with whom we have a business relationship. We encourage you to read their Privacy Policies carefully. We may also link to websites that are maintained by one or more of our business partners who are collecting your information pursuant to their own policies.

**Deleting and Editing Forum Posts**

There is no option to delete your own posts, but you may contact support@Awesemo.com with any concerns you have. Deleting posts often disrupts the general flow of forum threads, as other posters have likely responded to the community’s comments and generated additional discussion. Awesemo.com reserves the right to delete any post at any time.

**Consent to Display Information**

Awesemo.com reserves the right to display any information you submit in your profile, including, but not limited to, real name and screen names(s).

**Contact Us**

Email us at support@Awesemo.com with any questions you may have related to our Privacy Policy.
